noteflight.com 2015-09-08

# Noteflight - Privacy Policy

Loading... If the site doesn't appear or is incomplete, please reload this page. If the problem persists, please [contact Support.](http://feedback.noteflight.com/)

Noteflight Privacy Policy

Noteflight is committed to protecting the privacy of our Users' personal information. This statement applies with respect to the information that we collect from our web site, located at noteflight.com.

**I. GENERAL INFORMATION COLLECTED**

We collect non-personally identifiable information about you in a number of ways, including tracking your activities through your domain name (but not your e-mail address), aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, computer settings or most-recently visited URL. We do not collect any personally identifiable information about you unless you voluntarily submit such information to us, by, for example, filing out a survey or registration form.

**II. PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION**

The information we collect may include your name and contact information, gender, birth date, occupation and industry, behavior patterns, and other information.

**III. USE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED**

**A. USE OF GENERAL INFORMATION.** We collect non-identifying, general, generic and aggregate information in order to better design our Web site and services, and share the aggregate data with advertisers and other third parties.

**B. USE OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION.** Any contact information you provide will only be used by us to contact you. If you supply Noteflight with your postal address on-line you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address. No other third party receives your personally identifiable information.

**IV. COOKIES**

Noteflight makes use of cookies to: (a) store information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit Noteflight; (b) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (c) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.

**V. CHILDREN**

Noteflight is not intended for use by children under 13, and we do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13. Children aged 13 or older should not submit any personal information without the permission of their parents or guardians. By using Noteflight, you are representing that you are at least 18, or that you are at least 13 years old and have your parents' permission to use the service.

**VI. CHANGES IN USE OF INFORMATION.** From time to time, Noteflight may use User information for new, innovative and unanticipated purposes not previously disclosed or described in this privacy policy. Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on the Noteflight web site. If you are concerned about how we are using your information, please check our web site periodically. Your continued use of this site following the posting of any modification or change will constitute your acceptance thereof.

If you wish to limit the ways that we use your information please contact us. Upon request we provide site visitors with access to all information (including proprietary information) that is maintained on them.

**VII. OTHER WEB SITES; LINKS**

Noteflight provides links to other web sites. Noteflight is not responsible for the privacy practices or content on other web sites. We strongly suggest that you read a web site's privacy policy before submitting personal information or utilizing the resources of that site.   

Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us.

Defined terms used herein and not defined elsewhere have the meanings prescribed thereto in the Terms of Use posted separately on noteflight.com.
